I carry high my craven flag,
my ally I'm gonna fly and let my
struggles shoot me through the sky!
It'd be a pity if we
lingered here and let our
pretty sparks of life
blend aloud and disappear?
There may be fog that even you can't
navigate If someone strong like you is lost,
then who will set me straight?
Cause when the waves
cast, my heart adrift.
It's been your kindness and your strength.
That would free me from the mist.
And just like that.
We move on.
Sail to a new dawn.
Weigh anchor, ride as high as you can.
I assure I don't need anger.
I go fast as I am, yeah.
I hear you laughing like
you're numb to it all.
While we're dashing together.
No, we're never gonna fall, you know.
The whole world may now be my enemy.
Water swirl, but I ain't backing
down so long as I'm free, yeah.
Thought I'd give it, come
round the current with me.
All in, wake up bright and
early, making for the peak we go.
You may look different, but you're
as impudent as ever. Good to know.
Your mind and body have caught
up to your Devil Fruit powers.
That's what it means to reach a wakening.
What a ridiculous transformation.
I've worked so hard to build this place.
And now you've taken so
much of it away from me.
My crew and my castle are in ruins.
And what have you lost?
We've lost some, but we'll take
way more back when I'm through!
Candle Dragon Swarm!
How about this?
Now we're having a ball!
Ouch!
Every floor of the castle is on fire,
and it seems to be spreading fast.
I'm sure your crew and thousands
of soldiers are suffering inside.
Soon there'll be nothing but ash.
I'm not worried at all. They're tough.
I left that job to them, and
I know my friends can do it.
All I need to focus on is
kicking your scaly ass!
Your stupid laugh is pissing me off.
Demolition God!
Oh, the towers are burning, too!
Where the hell are we supposed to run now?
You guys, it's me!
Where did everybody go?
Anybody?
Hello?
Chopper!
Nami!
You okay?
There's too much fire!
Poor Zoro, and Sanji, and Franky,
Brook, Usopp, Robin, and Jinbei too!
They must be in the fire!
How can we put it out?
This is a real mess.
We're trapped.
Even if we find the rest of the crew,
the entire island is one big inferno.
Where would we go?
Unless Onigashima lands,
we're not safe anywhere.
Hey, Zeus, can't you use your
rain to help put out the fire?
It's too intense!
What if I get burned?
We all worked really hard to get here.
It can't end like this when we're
so close to winning. We'll be fine.
There's no way Luffy's gonna lose.
So don't give up!
Damn it! We're screwed!
There's nowhere to go!
I'm cooking over here!
Damn it!
I'm slowly dying.
I think I'm...
I think I'm dead.
I'm not hauling your corpse! Don't die!
No!
If there's a way out, I don't see it.
I'm afraid this might be it.
Captain, come save us!
We need you!
Oh dear, my precious afro is
getting even frizzier. This is bad.
At this rate, I'll end
up looking like you.
What?
One skeleton!
May your poor, tortured
soul rest at peace.
It breaks my heart just looking at you.
No one deserves to be such a cruel end.
Burn to the bone!
This terrible fire!
I fear it'll take us all! Oh, no.
I'm not a burnt corpse.
I am dead, though.
This is becoming a bit
oppressive, isn't it?
I fear there may be no way out for us!
So it seems.
Damn it, we can't get outside.
The whole yard is gone.
Oh no.
An endless abyss in front
and a hellish fire behind us.
We're stuck and couldn't
turn back if we wanted to.
Unfortunately,
we're stuck in the air, surrounded
by fire with the island collapsing.
We'll come up with something.
Just wait.
We all know it's hot, okay?
Break the damn wall!
If we stay in this spot
long, we're gonna die!
Better to lose an arm than lose your life!
What's the point of those giant
muscles if you're not gonna use them?
Oh, you wanna fight?
Then bring it!
I'm running, but frankly,
I don't know where.
A suggestion would be welcome.
Don't ask me.
If I had any ideas, I'd tell you.
We'll all suffocate to death at this rate.
Just keep running.
There is no more I can do.
Please help.
I can give it a try.
I've got one trick.
Special attack Green Star Sprinkler!
There's a word that comes to
mind, and that word is failure.
Shut up!
I'm trying to work here.
I've got to keep my promise to Iso.
I need to save Keen and Kiku,
and myself, of course, too.
Oh!
What of me?
Surely I'm worth saving, too!
This fire's crazy.
It needs to chill.
Where are we supposed to go?
Sora's not gonna make it at this rate.
I gotta get him to chop her
before he kicks the bucket.
If we don't do something
about the fire, we'll be dead.
I'm done for! I'm done for!
Will somebody save me?
Hope was so.
Please, big bro.
Shut your traps.
Complaining ain't gonna do deadly.
Don't make me leave you here.
We promise we'll behave.
We're sorry, sir.
We hit another dead end. Damn it.
If it's not the fire,
then it's the debris.
Did somebody do this on
purpose to lock us in?
If I die in battle, I can accept that.
Then I'm sure as hell not
going to burn to death.
What kind of fight is this?
This damn fire won't get the best of me.
Or me we'll pull through.
Let us proceed with the plan searching
bay with haste if you don't mind?
Thank you for placing your faith in me.
I will not fail of course Luffy
formed an alliance with you samurai.
I would never doubt your worth
Alright, I'm ready
Very well, my trusted new ally.
Let us see this through.
I have been prepared for
this since that accursed day.
Answer me!
Lord Omonosuke!
Lady Hiyoti!
This way, and make taste!
To my shame, I couldn't
save Lord Odin that day.
I allowed Lord Momonosuke and the
others to suffer in those flames.
Even with the power of my
ninjutsu, I still failed.
I have no greater regret.
That feeling of helplessness.
That failure.
Never again!
So?
I've never seen rain like that before.
This is how Zunesha takes a bath.
Causing a mighty downpour
in the process, huh?
I could use this.
My brave friends.
I will not let you perish in this fire!
This time I'm ready.
I'm sorry that I kept you waiting so long?
The water that I borrowed
from Zunesha's back.
Shall flow once again!
Now, ninpo!
Scrolling jutsu!
Summon the elephant's back!
Ani-chi-ri!
Restoration!
This certainly is a lot!
Water art!
Fish and jutsu!
Ocean Current Sildercrow!
Make your way through every hall!
The walkers of Zed shall
deliver you from this hell!
You don't have to carry me like this are
you kidding me this is the leaf we can do i
know You're banged
up what should we do
there's nowhere for us
to go what's that noise
Sounds like something's coming
It's water
We're not going to die
Get to work Momonosuke! Why?
Kaido is still alive, isn't he?
You need to be the one holding
up the island, not him!
So start making flame clouds!
Support the entire island myself?
That is simply not possible!
Kaido's wearing down. It won't hold.
If we wait, all of our allies might die.
What?
We've nearly won this, but
you still must do your part.
Your people need you!
What?!
This was the only choice
we had from the start!
To save Wano, you must protect Onigashima!
Come on, Momonosuke!
Make those flame clouds now!
You can't lose focus.
You have to try.
That's easier said than done!
They won't come out.
I'm useless.
I'm too weak.
Momonosuke.
You must go along with
Kin'emon and the others.
You must travel 20 years into the
future and rebuild the Kozuki clan.
That's too much to ask!
Get you and Iori!
Come with me at least!
Lord Momonosuke, your mother is suffering
far more from this than you are.
This is the land of samurai where you
must maintain honor or face death.
This brave woman has
displayed unflinching resolve.
A man cannot show cowardice
in the face of that.
It would be an unbearable shame.
I'm a child.
There's nothing I can do.
Lord Odin has left us.
So with all due respect, you are
no longer just an ordinary child.
You are the sun and the air.
of a distinguished Samanai.
And that means you will be
Shogun of this country someday.
If the young Lord will not go,
then I have one final request.
May we go forth to fight
our enemies once more.
If I stay here, I will only burn to death.
Please let me die like a Samanai,
fighting with sword in hand.
Give us this mercy.
Let us serve our fallen Lord,
as we have all vowed to do!
Momonosuke?
Hear me, Mother!
I've decided.
I will go.
This is farewell.
Farewell.
Please, live on, my son.
But how can I show my face to mother now?
I am not a mere child.
I am not weak or useless.
I am the man who will become
Shogun of this country!
I will save the land of
Wano and stop Onigashima!
Wait, no!
I said stop, not go faster!
Oh, gum!
Lightning!
Grabbing lightning
straight from the clouds.
You think you're clever?
Oh, what an absurd power.
Boing, boing.
You bastard!
Ha-ha-ha!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Here we go!
Has this become a game to you?
Then play around all you like.
But remember...
It'll take more than a
Devil Fruit to win this war.
Wadju showed us the
truth with his strength.
He became king without a Devil Fruit
power to rely on because in the end
Haki trumps all else
destroyer of death
thunder
fadwa
To the ones we've lost, set sail!
Let your sky boat fly!
The festival's almost over.
It's funny, I'd almost
forgotten that I'm a slave.
I hope I can survive another
year to see this again.
Ready, Daddy?
Find my daddy up there!
What the hell?
Get your grubby hand off me!
That's supposed to be a joke!
You're making yourself an easy target!
Dragon twister!
Demolition bird!
I assume you're still vulnerable!
To cutting attacks in your new form!
Come on Straw Hat!
Get your ass down here!
Wait!
The nail came free!
That last tremor has released
me from this hellish prison!
If I can't escape, I'll at
least take you down with me!
Are you watching, Odin?
Your daughter is at my mercy!
WE'RE GOING TO HELL TOGETHER!
Are you okay, boss?
From the looks of things,
Onigashima's about to fall.
Then Kaido's starting
to lose. That's good.
Well, we have two options.
I'll let you decide. If Mr.
Straw Hat beats Kaido, the
island falls down and we all die.
Option two we make it out alive
because Kaido survives the battle.
You kidding?
Well that's easy enough.
I have a kid back in Hakumai
that I'm fighting for.
And I'm fighting for
my wife back in Ringo.
If Kaido gets his ass kicked, our
families can live happily ever after.
It'll be a great country.
Everyone down there will
have a bright future?
Are you samurai out of your damn minds?
You won't be alive to enjoy it, you know?
And that's fine by us.
Make Kaido pay!
Don't hold back, Straw Hat!
We came here to win this fight!
We won't back down!
I don't want to die!
I refuse to die!
No fire to get the best of me!
Encore! Encore!
Water!
Kiku! Kill him on!
We can't give up!
No matter what!
Stop! Onigashima!
Hey!
Dome!
I'm about to wrap this fight up, but you've
got to move that island out of the way!
This fist is huge.
He could punch a hole straight
through Onigashima with that thing.
Stop!
Wait, Luffy!
I'm not ready yet! Mama!
You got this!
I trust you!